Hello
مرحبا
and welcome back to our English listening practice.
ومرحبا بعودتنا إلى ممارسة الاستماع إلى اللغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
I hope you're doing well.
آمل أن تكون بخير.
Today's practice is all about something
ممارسة اليوم تدور حول شيء ما
we all need to do, going to the supermarket.
كلنا بحاجة للذهاب إلى السوبرماركت.
If you live in another country
إذا كنت تعيش في بلد آخر
or if you're just traveling
أو إذا كنت تسافر فقط
you might find supermarkets a little confusing.
قد تجد السوبرماركت مربكة بعض الشيء.
Where is the Halal meat section?
أين قسم اللحوم الحلال؟
Do they sell dates?
هل يبيعون التمر؟
What if you want to ask about
ماذا لو أردت أن تسأل عن ذلك؟
Saudi products for cooking?
منتجات سعودية للطهي؟
These are great questions
هذه أسئلة رائعة
and today I will help you
واليوم سأساعدك
In this story, I will take you with me
في هذه القصة، سآخذك معي
on a trip to the supermarket.
في رحلة إلى السوبرماركت.
You will learn useful English phrases
ستتعلم عبارات إنجليزية مفيدة
to help you when you go shopping.
لمساعدتك عندما تذهب للتسوق.
I will speak slowly and clearly
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so please listen carefully.
لذا أرجو أن تستمعوا جيدا.
If you want, you can repeat after me.
إذا أردت، يمكنك التكرار بعدي.
This will help you understand English better
هذا سيساعدك على فهم الإنجليزية بشكل أفضل
and make your speaking stronger step by step.
واجعل حديثك أقوى خطوة بخطوة.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Let’s begin
لنبدأ